

# MARKO GOBELJIC FULL STACK ENGINEER

# **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

# Languages:

JavaScript, TypeScript, PHP, Python

# Front-end Frameworks

React, Vue, Electron, Flutter Web

#### **Back-end Frameworks:**

Node.js, Express, Nest.js, Net, Laravel, Django

# **Mobile App Frameworks**

React Native. Flutter

# **Cloud Services:**

AWS Amplify, AWS Lambda, Amazon DynamoDB, S3, AWS Cognito, EC2, Cloud Firestore, Firebase Realtime database, Firebase gateway

# DevOps:

Github, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Docker, CI/CD, Webpack, Jest, Mocha, Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Waterfall, TDD, SOLID, DRY

## **Engineering & Technology:**

Software Engineering, Reverse Engineering, Artificial Intelligence

# CONTACT DETAILS

# Address:

Novi Sad, Vojvodina, Serbia

#### LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/marko-gobeljic

#### **Email**:

gobeljic.mmarko@gmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

Faculty of Technical Sciences, University of Novi Sad (2008 -2011) Computer Science | Bachelor's Degree

# **EXECUTIVE PROFILE**

I am a full-stack developer having more than 8+ years of experience in building web and mobile applications.

I'm a full stack, a polyglot developer who is constantly learning how to make web/hybrid apps faster, leaner, and perfectly designed. I have worked on +30 CMS, CRM, Mobile, Analysis, Blockchain, eCommerce sites so far.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Self Employed | Jun 2021 - Present

- Developed headless CMS with React.js, Node.js, and Strapi
- Upgraded a powerful SaaS using Vue.js and Vuex, Vuetify framework
- Updated and added new RESTful APIs by using Apollo GraphQL + AWS Lambda function

## **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

**ACTANO GmbH | Jun 2019 - Jun 2021** 

- Used the React-Redux, Redux-Saga based on MVC Architecture patterns and TDD
- Used Material UI to implement the design
- Built Storybook Components & Tailwind CSS
- Built Mutation, Queries, Schema, Type, Validation, Caching, and Pagination by using the Apollo GraphQL
- Implemented video stream to show real-time status in the parking area

# SR. FULL STACK DEVELOPER (REACT | NODE)

ACTANO GmbH | Sep 2018 - May 2019

- Improved a FinTech platform in the Frontend side and API implementation in React
- Added 30+ components to be used in the global app by using styled components.
- Worked with JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Al, d3.js, Algorithms, Al,
  MI
- Automated testing suites, like Jest
- · DevOps such as CI/CD, Jenkins

#### SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

MyContainer | Apr 2017 - Sep 2018

- UI/UX from custom graphic design to React/Typescript-based components.
- Improved performance by optimizing codes with modern JS and API handling.
- Keep the quality with automated testing.
- Suggested and Integrated real-time communication mechanism with Socket.IO and ws(npm package)

## SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

MyContainer | Aug 2016 - Mar 2017

- Used semantic component framework Vuetify.js which supports server-side.
- Using the Tailwind CSS because it is much faster and easier to build and refactor UI.
- Managing the Migration, Seeding, Eloquent model, Routing, Authentication, Middleware, ORM, Unit testing, Artisan in Larayel.
- Used the Laravel packages like Spark, Cashier, Vapor, Horizon, and many others.

#### FULL STACK WEB AND MOBILE DEVELOPER

HotLap | Jan 2014 - Aug 2016

- Implemented a RESTful Node.js server as the lead back-end developer.
- Deployed to AWS and maintained the servers with basic Linux administration.
- Created reusable D3.js charts using Raphael.js to draw SVG on browsers.

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Netfork | Feb 2012 - Mar 2014

- Worked on enterprise-level Supply Chain and Logistics web applications using Angular and TypeScript.
- Developed and improved performance of +10 animation effects with custom styling
- This project is currently used by McKesson, AWS, and other partners.
- Collaborated with team members through Slack and Azure DevOps.